[distant siren wailing]
[distant horn blaring]
[tires squealing]
Come on.
Get inside now!
[engine revving]
[tires squealing]
Suspect went inside.
SWAT. secure the perimeter.
I want every door covered.
Roger that.
[tense music]
♪ ♪
Set.
SWAT. breach the door!
Execute!
♪ ♪
Take it!
[explosion booms]
- Get them out of there now!
- Fall back!
Fall back!
[groaning]
[gunshots]
Get down!
Ugh!
Shots fired!
[gunshots continue]
They've got rifle ports.
We don't have an angle.
Guys. this whole building might
be rigged with explosives.
We need to find another way
into that building.
Law enforcement are in
pursuit of three armed men
who gained entry to the
Best Merch corporate offices.
gunning down senior
vice president Robert Pearson
before escaping.
Where are my eyes. Ian?
Any second now.
OK. we're live.
OK.
Yeah. yeah. yeah.
Looks like a war zone out there.
Where are we?
ADIC Green.
Well. we've initiated
a multi-agency response.
Our team pursued
the suspect from the scene
to a secondary location. where
we now have them surrounded.
Then why are we still outside?
Oh. the building
is rigged with IEDs.
You got an open line?
Uh. yeah. sure.
You're speaking
to Special Agent Zidan.
OA. listen up.
ADIC Green.
What are we waiting for?
Let's breach that building.
[gunshots]
- Scene is not secure. sir.
Taxpayers pay good money
to train SWAT
for events just like this.
Get us in there.
Sir. we do not have eyes inside.
They have rifle ports
and explosive traps.
I called for a Bearcat.
When it gets here.
we will breach. not before.
I trust Special Agent Zidan
literally in
any tactical situation.
[tense music]
How long till that Bearcat?
Still 15 minutes out.
[crashing]
[explosion booms]
Move. move. move!
♪ ♪
Bearcat was the right call.
Agent Zidan knows
what he's doing.
♪ ♪
Watch out for tripwires.
Mark it.
♪ ♪
Scola. any eyes on our suspects?
No. there's no sign over here.
[distant chattering]
♪ ♪
Maps and plans specifically
targeting Pearson.
These are not lone gunmen.
This is a base of operations.
SWAT. any movement outside?
Negative.
All quiet.
Where the hell did they go?
We had the place surrounded.
I don't know.
Hey. guys.
Open this.
They must have got
out here when we were
waiting for the Bearcat.
Jubal. I think they got out
through a hatch in the floor.
We're going to follow.
see where it goes.
OK. this way.
Come on.
♪ ♪
Jubal. they're gone.
Guys. you need to see this.
♪ ♪
The unit searched the area
where the tunnel led out.
Suspects were long gone.
The NYPD is establishing
a wider dragnet.
but I'm not holding my breath.
- All right.
What about the bones that
we found at the scene?
No DNA match in CODIS.
but ERT did recover
a titanium stem
from what looks to be
a hip replacement.
They're using it
to track down a name.
They stride into
the corporate headquarters
of a Fortune 100 company
in broad daylight
and assassinate the senior VP.
Who the hell are these guys?
Your team managed
to pull partial prints
from the hideout.
You're not going to like it.
Hunter Bach. Mike Crosby.
Wilson Corya.
All late 30s.
OK. but do we know them?
In a word.
They're all suspected members
of the Alameda Underground.
[suspenseful music]
- AU. the old terror group?
- That's right.
Back in 2012.
they splintered off
from the Occupy protests
in Portland.
Yeah. and back then.
the AU waged a violent campaign
targeting symbols
of American capitalism.
bank bombings. kidnapping
corporate executives.
Oh. but we snuffed them out
over a decade ago.
FBI went in and raided
their compounds in Oregon.
We got their major players.
Well. apparently not.
Not all of them.
A few have been
running dark ever since.
biding their time.
And now they're back
in New York.
launching a new wave of terror.
There's no telling
what other horrific attacks
this group has planned.
So let me be very clear.
The AU will not evade us again.
Not on my watch.
Find them.
Yes. sir.
You wanted to see me?
Yeah. come on in.
Shut the door.
Special Agent Zidan. you were
given a direct order today.
and you ignored it.
With all due respect.
tactical decisions reside
with the on-scene commander.
I figured if we went
in any earlier
that our team would have
sustained even more injuries.
Or they would have succeeded.
We'll never know.
What we do know is that
three domestic terrorists
evaded our capture today
because of your decision.
Look. I want to get these
guys just as bad as you do.
I will do whatever it takes
to bring them into our custody.
That won't be necessary.
I'm assigning you to 24-hour
surveillance of this woman.
June Taxera.
She's the ex-wife
of the AU founder.
You're benching me.
Reassigning you.
If any members of the AU
pop their head above ground
to pay June Taxera a visit.
you will be
waiting and watching.
She was only married to the
leader of AU for six months.
She's never been attached
to any of their activities.
This is a non-viable lead.
This is a waste of our time.
Anyone with even
the slightest connection
to this group is
now on our radar.
Surveilling her is
part of this case.
You failed to follow orders
once. Special Agent Zidan.
Maybe you'll do better
this time around.
You're dismissed.
[tense music]
♪ ♪
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm
Where are you going?
He's sending me to Bay Ridge
on some BS surveillance op.
You're kidding me.
I didn't sign up
for this. Maggie.
to follow some boss's ego
into a death trap.
What are we even doing here?
- I don't know.
Been asking myself
the same question for months.
Come up with any answers?
No. just showing up
and doing the work.
trying to quiet
the rest of the noise.
Does that work in Bay Ridge?
[birds chirping]
Special Agent Zara Ushruf.
Special Agent Zidan.
Who'd you piss off?
ADIC Green.
What about you?
Let's just say when
someone gives you permission
to speak freely. don't.
Come on.
Let's go set up our kit.
Pretty nice place
they got us here.
Spared no expense.
All right. Ian.
what have we got?
Yeah. the titanium stem
found in the charred remains
was from a hip replacement.
Serial number ID'd our vic
as Ana Montero.
OK. she another radical member
of the Alameda Underground?
More like a beloved
kindergarten teacher
from PS 36.
- What?
Yeah. I called Ana's school.
They said she hadn't been
to work in three days.
More alarming. her husband
told the principal
that his wife was just
down with a migraine.
Oh. OK.
So who's her husband?
That's where it
gets interesting.
Darcio Montero.
Used to live in Portland.
worked in demolition.
was a suspected member of AU.
So why wasn't he
picked up back in 2012
with the rest of his crew?
He wasn't named
in the indictment.
The week the Alameda
Underground got busted.
Darcio moved to Queens.
Three years later.
he marries Ana.
Guy's got no arrests. not even
an overdue library book.
I mean. he's lived
a quiet life ever since.
So it sounds like Darcio
is back to his old ways.
Can we ping his phone?
- Yep. got a hit.
All right. bring him in.
Let's see what he says.
I told you. I got...
I got nothing to do with
the Alameda Underground.
So...
That what you told
your wife too?
Except she didn't believe you.
So then you felt like
you had to take matters
into your own hands.
What are you talking about?
We found her. Darcio...
burned in a barrel. AU hideout.
Uh. no.
No.
What are you...
what are you saying?
What. are you...
are you saying that Ana is...
Ana is dead?
Are you being serious right now?
Is this for real?
[banging on table]
[sobbing]
She wasn't involved
in any of this!
She was not involved.
and they... they kill her?
Hold up. hold up.
Who killed her?
Your AU buddies?
My buddies?
I walked away from the AU
13 years ago!
All right. I'm not involved
in any of that!
But you were back in Seattle.
Yes. Yes.
I joined the AU
to... to wake people up.
All right?
Capitalism was the enemy.
Then the group started
getting so... so radical
and then so cruel.
I...
[exhales]
I... I walked away.
And Ana knew about my past.
And she loved me in spite of it.
So if you left it all behind.
how'd she get mixed up
in it. man?
[somber music]
Four... four days ago.
Hunter came by my work.
This is Hunter Bach?
Yeah.
And he said the world
needed AU again.
And he wanted your help.
He wanted my dynamite.
He knew that I started
working in demo again.
so he knew that I had access.
But I... I held the line.
I told him no way. and that...
and that I had left
that life behind me.
So he kidnapped your
wife for leverage.
He told me if I ever wanted
to see Ana alive again.
that I needed to bring
dynamite to a dead drop
and that once they had it.
they would text me
where to find her.
And have you already
dropped that dynamite off?
A few hours ago.
I was just waiting for them
to tell me where to find Ana.
but they never call...
they never called.
Darcio. where's the next target?
I don't know.
I... I gave them...
I gave them 20 sticks.
I mean. with that. they could...
they could take down
just about anything
they wanted to.
♪ ♪
Isobel. we need OA on this.
Maggie. it wasn't my call.
I was able
to convince ADIC Green
not to report it to OPR.
so OA will not face
disciplinary action.
He didn't do anything wrong.
Maggie. ADIC Greene is just
finding his footing upstairs.
All eyes are on him. so
let's give the man some grace.
- [sighs]
- Tell me.
Will Darcio cooperate?
- Yeah.
Ever since he found out that
the Alameda Underground
killed his wife.
he's desperate to.
But he gave them the dynamite.
20 sticks.
stashed them in a duffel
in a trash can
in the East Village.
ERT already combed the area.
but AU already got to it.
Do we know how they're
communicating with him?
Yes. on a burner
that we can't trace.
But he did just get a text from
Hunter Bach instructing Darcio
to meet him tomorrow morning
at Forest Park
to be reunited with his wife.
Except Ana is already dead.
Yeah. it's clearly a trap.
Yeah.
If you think Darcio will help.
let's put him in play.
[sighs] This is ridiculous.
June Taxera is peripheral
to this case at best.
Irrelevant at worst.
And yet. our orders are
to never leave this room
and log every time she eats.
sleeps. or showers.
Whoa. do not undersell it.
We also get to log every hour
of Game Show Network
she watches.
[sighs]
This lady lives
for "Wheel of Fortune."
[line ringing]
Oh. hang on.
Chabra Dialysis Clinic.
How may I help you?
Hi. Uzi.
Sorry to call so late.
- Right.
- It's June Taxera.
I just wanted to confirm
my weekly session.
Yo. June. hey.
Yeah. you're all set.
So I'll just see you Tuesday.
Yep. I'll see you then.
[line clicks]
[sighs] Real riveting stuff.
Logging it.
Is it messed up I hope
this dialysis center
is a front for
an extremist cell?
[chuckles]
What?
Nothing.
I was just thinking that
if I have to be sidelined.
at least it's with you.
What?
- You're sending mixed signals.
You ghosted me.
- I didn't ghost you.
- Yeah. you did.
- Habibti. it was Ramadan.
Don't "habibti" me.
Look. Zara.
I just got out
of a long relationship.
No. I get it.
You're not ready.
It's fine.
We can just focus
on the assignment.
♪ ♪
Yeah.
[sighs] OK.
♪ ♪
[sighs]
OK. Darcio. hope you had
your morning coffee.
Here's the plan.
OK. you're gonna sit
on the bench and wait.
[suspenseful music]
You with me?
Yeah.
OK.
Second anybody
from the AU shows up...
Hunter. anybody else...
we're gonna move in
and snatch them up. all right?
Yeah. OK.
You got any questions?
Hmm?
No.
OK.
I need to speak with you both.
♪ ♪
This guy is checked out.
I'm not putting him
anywhere near this.
You know. something's up.
He did just lose his wife.
He's grieving. no?
Yeah. I think
he wants vengeance.
I mean. there's no telling
what he's going to do
when those suspects show up.
Well. we can't lose
our advantage here.
So what's the play?
We get creative.
♪ ♪
All right.
I'm in position here.
How do I look?
Mm. it'll work in a pinch.
Just keep your head down.
Got it.
All right.
Eva. you see anything?
No. nothing yet.
OK. we've got
a green sedan pulling up.
OK. is it Hunter?
Mm. checking.
[computer beeping. whirring]
It's Wilson Corya.
He's heading down
the stairs behind you.
Copy.
I'm gonna circle around
to get behind him.
♪ ♪
Darcio?
Darcio. come on. man.
Just come with me.
I'll take you to Ana.
Son of a bitch.
♪ ♪
FBI. stop!
[grunts]
[gunshots]
[shouting]
[gunshot]
[grunts]
Suspect down.
♪ ♪
Pop the trunk.
Corya is dead.
No dynamite.
I repeat. there's no dynamite.
You were supposed to wake
me up to switch shifts.
You didn't have to be
on duty all night.
Yeah. no use in both of us
being exhausted.
Right?
Ah. I made us some coffee.
OK. well. what did I miss?
She scramble some eggs
for breakfast?
She actually fried them.
But check this out.
Our laser mic picked up
that she took
three different showers
this morning.
Three?
But we heard June on the phone.
She just got a new
dialysis port put in.
You're not supposed
to get those wet for. like.
two weeks. so no showers.
So what is she doing in there?
My point exactly.
What if she's making secret
calls from inside her bathroom?
Well. we have her phone tapped.
We would hear it.
Unless she has a burner.
If June thinks her house
is being bugged.
maybe she's using the water
to obscure her phone calls.
Old-school OPSEC.
OK. maybe June is involved
in all of this.
We have to call it in.
Or we confirm it ourselves.
All we need is ears
inside of her bathroom.
And our kit came with
one of these bad boys.
Omar. please don't
make tactical decisions
because you're bored.
We're already on thin ice.
Yeah. with an ADIC
who thinks he knows better
and has never done field work
a day in his life.
OK. sure. but we still
need a warrant for the bug.
Unless we believe these are
exigent circumstances.
Do we believe that?
I believe we could believe that.
I'll call the AUSA.
get the ball rolling.
We'll follow up with
a search warrant affidavit.
But if June is calling someone
from the Alameda Underground.
and they're planning
another attack.
we cannot afford
not to hear that call.
All right.
so our agents took down
one of our prime suspects.
Wilson Corya.
But his partners.
Mike Crosby and Hunter Bach.
are still at large
and in possession
of the missing dynamite.
So what is the AU planning
to do with all that firepower?
We got no hits on our BOLOs.
no chatter on the wires.
I may have a lead.
Yeah. leads for the win.
What's up?
Well. ERT processed
Wilson's car.
They found a crumpled
parking ticket in the vehicle.
It was issued
at 2:47 p.m. yesterday.
I already pulled street
camera footage from the area.
Yeah. yeah. yeah.
All right. can you zoom in?
All right. there's our
Alameda Underground members.
Hunter Bach. Mike Crosby.
and Wilson Corya.
Darcio said he put
the dynamite in a duffel.
Scrub forward.
[tense music]
So the three
enter this building.
While they're inside.
they get a ticket.
♪ ♪
Ten minutes later.
Wilson exits alone.
No sign of the bag
or his partners.
Then Wilson finds
the ticket and leaves.
Three terrorists and a bag of
dynamite walk into a building.
- Don't know that one.
- Yeah. me neither.
So what's inside the building?
OK. it's the editorial offices
for "The Borough Progressive."
It's a far-left newspaper.
It's been around forever.
So their politics align
with the Alameda Underground's.
right?
So why would the AU target them?
Well. we drove a Bearcat
through their old hideout.
What if this is their
new base of operations?
FBI!
This is a raid!
All right. we need everyone
to stop what you're doing
and leave while
we search the premises.
Come on.
- You heard her.
Let's go.
Leave your computers.
Follow our agents outside.
Thank you.
Excuse me.
I'm the editor of this paper.
Where are you taking my staff?
We're detaining them until
our search is complete.
We're looking for two members
of the Alameda Underground
and we were told
that they were here.
The AU is active again?
This isn't some exclusive.
ma'am.
Have you seen
either of these men?
No. but I would like
to see a warrant.
I figured you
might ask for that.
You know. your
paper's ideology and theirs
couldn't be more aligned.
If you know where
they're hiding.
then start talking right now.
You think we're protecting them.
We haven't seen them.
They're not here.
Guess we'll see.
Just know we will
be writing about this.
Looking forward to reading that.
All right. let's fan out.
Search the entire building.
OK. she's gone.
You're clear.
♪ ♪
Go up the stairs.
Bathroom's on your right.
♪ ♪
[alert beeps]
She's headed back.
[clatters]
Please tell me
she didn't hear that.
Yeah. get the hell out of there.
I'm not done yet.
♪ ♪
[sighs]
OA. she's headed your way
and she's got a shotgun.
OK.
OK. um...
[tense music]
♪ ♪
[door bell ringing]
Be right there!
♪ ♪
Hey. neighbor.
I don't think we've met.
I'm Zara.
My husband and I just
moved in across the street.
I'm June.
Our cat actually got out. Omar.
I was wondering
if you'd seen him.
Oh. I sure don't think so.
Well. this is him. Omar.
Big fella.
You mind just
keeping an eye out?
Sure. I'll keep an eye out.
Great.
Thank you so much.
OK.
So it looks like
our two suspects
weren't among the employees.
Well. we know they were here.
so we gotta keep looking.
Maggie. we got the duffel.
Landslide!
Bomb!
Evacuate now!
Everyone out!
♪ ♪
[explosion booms]
[grunting and groaning]
[siren whoops]
[indistinct chatter]
So I counted six sticks
in that bag.
Darcio said that
he gave Hunter 20.
Any of this feel off to you?
Alameda Underground is
hardcore left-leaning.
So why are they blowing up
an independent.
progressive newspaper?
They're on the same side.
so something's not adding up.
That was incredible.
But your cat's name is Omar?
Just some stupid name
I came up with.
Well. it sounds like someone
can't keep me off their mind.
Don't flatter yourself.
It's OK.
Feeling's mutual.
Thought you were
getting over a breakup.
[beeping]
Bug's live.
June's taking another shower.
Well done. Hunter.
You did good.
Now it's time to move on
to the next target.
Did she just say "next target"?
OK. this one. we gotta call in.
OA. I have ADIC Green
here with me now.
Fill us in on what you know.
June Taxera appears
to be the shot caller
for the Alameda Underground.
And what makes you say that?
She just called someone
named Hunter and told them
to prepare
for their next attack.
Well. it has to be Hunter Bach.
And she made this call
from the landline?
It was a burner that
we didn't know about.
But how... how were
you close enough
to hear this conversation?
Our surveillance was impeded.
so we planted a bug
in her bathroom.
You didn't have a warrant
to plant any bug. Agent Zidan.
so all the evidence
you collected
would be inadmissible in court.
You've just jeopardized
our entire case.
No. we didn't. sir.
We reached out to the AUSA.
We got verbal authorization
from the magistrate.
OA. you should have spoke
with me before you made a move.
Apologies. ma'am.
It all happened very fast.
But if June Taxera is
planning another attack.
we need to bring her in
and brace her for intel.
You don't make those decisions.
That's my job.
And right now. I want you
to keep her in play
while we monitor
everything she does.
And if you learn anything new.
I will be the one
to make that decision.
Do I make myself clear?
[grim music]
Yes. sir.
♪ ♪
I don't think he likes you.
Well. this is why we do
widespread
network surveillance. people.
Lucky for us.
we had OA on this one.
All right. tell me
about June Taxera.
She's 63. former librarian
whose ex-husband founded the
Alameda Underground in 2011.
He died in a shootout
with FBI in 2013.
Was she ever a part
of the group?
Not to our knowledge.
They divorced after
he founded the group.
June moved to New York
and broke ties with him.
Well. she doesn't scream
terrorist mastermind.
Can we tie her
to today's attacks?
Well. OA reported that
she's using a burner.
but we don't have the number.
so can't exploit it.
Hey. guys.
I might have something.
Six days ago. June withdrew
her entire life savings.
$67.000 in cash from her bank.
That's a hefty withdrawal.
What did she want
with all that cash?
OK. yeah. I got that
street cam footage here.
Check it out.
That is June leaving
her bank six days ago.
Mm-hmm.
Cash must be in the grocery bag.
All right. let's see
if we can follow her.
See where she goes next.
OK. next.
she heads south for a bit
and then pick her up again.
heading into this building.
That is the
Chabra Dialysis Center.
Yeah. June has a co-pay
for dialysis once a week.
Yeah. OK. well. surely.
she's not paying
for her treatments in cash.
Let's fast forward
and see where she goes next.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah. OK. bag is gone.
So she must have handed
the cash to somebody
inside that clinic.
Right. so who would
have seen something?
One of the employees?
Wait. hold on.
According to OA's
surveillance log.
June made a call last night to
her dialysis nurse. Uzi Morris.
Yeah. yeah. yeah.
Let's see what he knows.
You're June Taxera's point
of contact at Chabra Clinic.
Is that right?
- Yeah.
I love June.
Is she OK?
Maybe you can tell us.
Last week. she walked
into your clinic
with $67.000 in cash
and left it there.
Did you see her give that
money to anybody in the clinic?
She gave it to me.
But I haven't done
anything wrong.
Other than aiding and abetting
a known domestic terrorist.
June?
Mr. Morris.
we believe that June is running
a violent terrorist
organization.
And this morning.
they killed this man.
Robert Pearson...
he's a father of two.
And then they blew up
an independent newspaper.
So if you know where
the next target is.
you better start
speaking right now.
I don't know.
I swear. I don't.
What was the money for?
Look. June's been coming
to my clinic for a few years.
She's had a tough time.
She's a fighter and a friend.
Friend or not. she set you up
to look like an accessory here.
I didn't do anything. OK?
A few weeks ago. June asked me
about online betting.
Heard me bragging
to the other nurses.
Sports betting?
You heard about decentralized
prediction markets?
You can bet on anything.
A lot of them are stupid.
but they can still pay out.
I've made some good money.
and it's all totally legal.
OK. so June was giving you
money to place her online bets?
Yeah.
Last week.
she shows up with cash.
Says she needed a lucky break.
Times being the way they are.
asked me to convert the cash
to crypto. set up an account.
And then I showed her how
to place a few bets online.
It's pretty easy
once you know how.
She mention
"The Borough Progressive"?
[sighs]
That was one of the bets.
actually.
Looks like she used you
as a cutout.
I'm an idiot.
I thought...
[sighs]
I figured she just
got crazy lucky.
and I was happy for her.
June's already at $1.4 million.
Sorry. $1.4 million?
All right. we're gonna need
the name of the site.
So June gets her dialysis nurse
to teach her how
to place online bets.
is a line of inquiry they
did not teach us in Quantico.
Yeah. looks like June's
been pumping her money
into a site called X-Probable.
It's one of several
platforms that skirt
state gambling laws by calling
itself a predictive market.
So how does it work?
Well. the site
has moderators that post
various predictions on almost
any event that's happening
in the real world.
- Yeah.
Yeah. you can bet on whether
Punxsutawney Phil
will see his shadow
or how long the upcoming
State of the Union will last.
Yeah. the site has
hundreds of different bets.
and they change all the time.
Yeah. it's a gambling
addict's dream come true.
It's also incredibly
vulnerable to manipulation.
It seems that's what June
has been doing all day.
According to this profile
Uzi set up for her.
June's first bet was who will
be the next CEO of Best Merch.
Robert Pearson or Tom Cord.
And it was expected
to be Pearson.
Yeah. and then
AU assassinated him.
and Tom Cord stepped in.
and cha-ching.
Yeah. and then her next bet.
will "The Borough Progressive"
go fully digital
by the end of the year?
A long shot.
given the paper's commitment
to staying in print.
Well. you'll be sure
to win that bet
if you blow up
the printing press.
Exactly.
The editor just announced
that after the explosion.
"The Borough" has no choice
but to go digital.
It's one thing
to know the outcome
and use insider information
to make a buck.
but the AU is forcing
these outcomes
through acts of terror.
Yeah. and then
using the windfall
to finance the most dangerous
domestic terror group
this country has seen
in a century.
[tense music]
Simon Ford.
Isobel.
Good to see you again.
Yes.
This is ADIC Green.
Simon's satellite
technology helped us
when Third Testament took down
our power grid last year.
Hmm.
Well. thank you for coming in
on such short notice.
Unfortunately. my next-gen
CADO headsets aren't ready yet.
Well. actually.
we need your help
with one of your other
many ventures. X-Probable.
Ah.
All the rage these days.
You didn't strike me
as a gambler.
No. but I really like
being the house.
Our moderators pick
the prop bets.
and then we charge a
transaction fee on every user.
Adds up to millions.
Well. we have evidence that
a terrorist group is profiting
and manipulating
your market's platform.
A terrorist group?
They go by Vantage489
on your site.
We need access to this
account to find out
if there have been
any new bets placed.
[suspenseful music]
[indistinct whispering]
My director of comms has
been kind enough to remind me
that user privacy is what
gives us an advantage
over our competitors.
If word were to get out that we
just gave the FBI full access
to our privileged data...
If the AU pulls off
another act of terror today.
your market shares would be
the least of your worries.
Give me the account name.
We need to know if Vantage489
has placed any new bets today.
Just texted my dev team.
If this user's made
any new bets.
they'll know about them.
Thank you.
[phone buzzing]
My God.
What?
What's the bet?
♪ ♪
All right. so June Taxera
also placed a massive bet
that the South Brooklyn
Marathon will be shut down.
Why would anyone bet on that?
OK. yeah. when it was
posted on X-Probable.
there was a low-pressure system
expected to bring heavy storms.
People thought it would
affect the marathon.
Site moderators wanted
to get in on the action.
But the weather changed.
and the storm went out to sea.
Yeah. but the bet
stayed on the site.
Can't we just take the bet down?
Well. I asked Simon Ford.
He's clearly dragging his feet.
He likes the action.
Yeah. all press is
good press. and all that.
But at least now we know
the AU is targeting that race.
and they want to shut it down.
Well. the race started
28 minutes ago.
Somebody show me the route.
So 26.2 miles
from Dyker Heights
to Bushwick and back.
That is a huge area to search.
Yeah. get our teams headed
in that direction.
and let's find a way
to narrow this down.
♪ ♪
[mouse clicking]
We should be out there.
doing something.
Yeah. but the boss's boss
doesn't like you. remember?
Shouldn't matter.
It's the only thing
that matters these days.
But the bureau is bigger
than any one man.
It is bigger than all of us.
It is an ideal
that we strive for.
And it is the greatest
privilege of my life. Zara.
That's really
inspiring stuff. Omar.
What?
I mean it.
I do.
If I'm going to be sidelined.
at least it's with you.
[monitor beeps]
Hunter. everyone ready?
Good.
June is taking another shower.
Mile marker 10.
And make it loud.
[ominous music]
[indistinct PA announcements]
- The 10th...
[cheers and applause]
[PA chatter continues]
You guys got anything?
Nothing yet.
Yeah. it looks like
we're all clear here.
Hold on.
I think I got eyes
on Mike Crosby.
Looks like a dark backpack.
gray ball cap.
Might be the rest
of the dynamite.
I got an angle on it.
Mike Crosby!
[tense music]
♪ ♪
FBI!
Stop!
Show me your hands!
[gunshot]
[crowd screaming]
♪ ♪
We got dynamite.
Get the bomb squad here
immediately.
All right. folks.
so Mike Crosby is down.
but Hunter Bach
is still at large.
So how do we find him?
Guys. you're going
to want to see this.
You got a lead on Hunter?
No. but a new prop bet
just appeared
on X-Probable's Top 10.
Will the leader of
the Alameda Underground
be apprehended today.
dead or alive?
Are you kidding me?
Simon Ford knows that we are
looking for June Taxera.
He took a private FBI briefing
and turned it into
a public prop bet.
And because of all
the news coverage.
the money's already flooding in.
thousands of bets.
On which side?
Dead or alive?
Take a wild guess.
♪ ♪
[grim music]
FBI.
June Taxera.
you're under arrest.
Oh!
I see you found your cat.
Save it. June.
It's over.
You wanna bet?
Omar.
Hunter Bach!
Zara. get her inside.
Drop your weapons!
I don't think so.
[gunshots]
[glass shatters]
What's happening?
Your friends aren't here
to rescue you.
They want you dead.
Why is Hunter trying to kill me?
The odds changed.
Your buddies could make
ten times the cash
if you end up dead.
OK. we're out of bullets.
- She needs medical.
- Backup's on the way.
June. where's that
shotgun you had?
I don't... I don't remember
where I left it.
OK. get her upstairs.
I'm gonna go look for it.
OK.
[tires squealing]
[tense music]
[gunshots]
- Going left.
- Covering!
I count four.
♪ ♪
OA. two coming
in the ground floor.
♪ ♪
Upstairs.
[grunts]
[panting]
One down up here.
[both grunting]
♪ ♪
[clattering]
[grunting]
[straining]
[gunshot]
[panting]
Hey. partner.
You miss me?
[sighs]
Hey. June.
I just wanted to let you know
that X-Probable is going
to dispute your wins
as market manipulation
and never going to pay you out.
And it turns out
even they draw the line
at aiding and abetting
domestic terrorism.
You don't get it.
This was never about
some noble ideal.
Well. what was it about?
The money?
Oh.
When you and your husband
started this group.
capitalism was the enemy.
It still is.
Look around.
I mean. living in this
country ain't cheap.
You're up.
Are you going to make me guess?
I'm being referred to OPR
for misconduct.
What?
It's OK.
You'll be fine.
You took the fall.
It was my idea to leave our post
and to plant the bug.
I don't know if this bureau
can live up to everything
that you said.
but I know that we have
a better chance
if you're in charge one day.
So let's keep your
record clean. shall we?
[gentle music]
♪ ♪
Zara.
Thank you.
♪ ♪
[tense music]
[wolf howls]
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm